formstack.com 2014-05-20

# Privacy Policy · Formstack

## Formstack Privacy Policy

### Summary

Formstack respects each individual's right to personal privacy. This Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how Formstack will collect, use and safeguard any personal information you provide. We will collect and use information only in the ways disclosed in this statement. All user information contained within any form you may use or build is governed by Formstack's [Terms and Conditions](https://www.formstack.com/terms). 

### Security

Formstack has implemented processes intended to protect user information and maintain security of data. Each account holder is assigned a unique user name and password, which is required to access their account. It is your responsibility to protect the security of this login information. We have attempted to protect Formstack's servers by locating them in areas with security procedures, use of firewalls and implementing other generally available security technologies. These safeguards help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of data, but no guarantee can be made that your information and data will be secure from intrusions and unauthorized release to 3rd parties.

### Application Data

As part of the Formstack services, we store the forms you build and any data that was collected from those forms. We respect the privacy of all users, and consider all data that is collected to be private. Your information is used strictly for internal purposes, and Formstack will not distribute or sell your information to a 3rd party, except as disclosed in this statement. The creator of a form may choose not to have the form data stored within the Formstack database, or may choose to encrypt the data in the database so that it will be impossible to access without a password that you specify. When you submit information, you are transferring such information into the United States and you hereby consent to such transfer.

### Account Information

We collect email addresses from those who contact us via email, and ask for information such as your email address and name when you sign up for an account with Formstack. The information we collect is not distributed or sold to a 3rd party. It will only be used to communicate with you about your Formstack account, and where needed as part of certain Formstack features. You may update your account information at any time.

### Web Server Logs

For statistical purposes, Formstack will gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. These log files contain standard information collected by web servers, such as client IP addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), operating system, etc. This information is only used internally, and is not distributed or sold to a 3rd party. Formstack uses this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the Formstack website and to gather demographic information about its user base as a whole. Formstack does not link this automatically collected data to personally identifiable information.

### Disclaimer

However, any information collected by Formstack may be shared if it is necessary to investigate, prevent or prosecute illegal activities, suspected fraud, violations to the Terms and Conditions, or as otherwise required by law or a valid government request (including, but not limited to, search warrants, subpoenas or court orders). Formstack may also share information if it is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Formstack will notify you before information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. Formstack reserves the right to use and disclose any information collected that is not in personally identifiable form.

### Cookies

A "cookie" is a small text file containing a unique identifier that our web server sends to a user's browser, and may be stored on a user's hard drive. Cookies are required to use Formstack services. If you have your browser set to reject cookies, your use of the Formstack services is likely to be interrupted. The cookies we use are not permanent.

### Online Advertising

Formstack participates in online advertising, including remarketing. Third party vendors, including Google, show Formstack ads on other sites on the internet. The vendors use cookies to serve Formstack ads based on a user's prior visits to the Formstack website. Users may opt out of a third party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

### Third-party Websites

Formstack is not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from the Formstack website, nor the information or content contained therein. When you use a link from the Formstack website to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to the Formstack website, is subject to that website's own rules and policies.

### Changes

Formstack reserves the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If material changes are made to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a prominent notice on the Formstack website home page.

### Compliance with Children's Online Privacy Protection Act

As a business service, Formstack does not target its offering toward, and does not knowingly collect any personal information from, users under thirteen (13) years of age.

### Safe Harbor

Formstack complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor framework and U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union countries and Switzerland. Formstack has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access and enforcement, as further explained in our [Safe Harbor Notice](https://www.formstack.com/safe-harbor).

### Terms of Use

Your use of the Formstack services is governed by our [Terms and Conditions](https://www.formstack.com/terms), which contains disclaimers, limitations of liability and a choice of Indiana law and jurisdiction.
